xyzhomework.com 2018-07-25

# XYZ Homework - Privacy Policy

## Start Here

Browser Check

Confirm that your browser is ready for our online homework system:

Check Now

## XYZ Homework Privacy Agreement

XYZ Homework may change any of the terms in this agreement at any time. Changes will become effective upon posting.

XYZ Homework will not disclose any personally identifiable information associated with your use of XYZ Homework (e.g. name, physical address, e-mail address, username and password, activity results) to any third parties except:

  1. within class rosters, grade books or communication tools (messaging system or class forums) that facilitate student-instructor or student-student conversations. Instructors have the ability to export grade book information from XYZ Textbooks to maintain educational records.
  2. where the information is requested by the student's educational institution or state educational officials for educational or administrative uses.
  3. where illegal conduct is suspected, personally identifiable information may be disclosed to instructors, educational institutions or law enforcement agencies in order to assist the investigation of potential illegal acts.

XYZ Homework reserves the right to use personally identifiable information to contact users for participation in focus groups or to test other products and services to users age 13 and over. XYZ Homework will not sell any such information to any third party.

XYZ Homework cannot be held responsible for any personally identifiable information you may voluntarily post in forums or send in messages through the XYZ Homework system.
